[

](https://www.pinger.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/our-products.svg)[

](https://textfree.us/)[

](https://www.sideline.com/)[

](https://getindex.com/)

[

](https://www.pinger.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/our-products.svg)[

](https://textfree.us/)[

](https://www.sideline.com/)[

](https://getindex.com/)

[

](https://www.pinger.com/)

Menu

Privacy Policy

**Overview**

This Privacy Policy describes how Pinger treats information that it collects and receives related to your use of Pinger’s products, services, and websites. Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide and improve our products and services.

**Children’s Personal Information**

All Pinger products, services and websites are not intended for children under the age of 13, so children under the age of 13 should not use them at any time.

Pinger does not knowingly collect any information from children under the age of 13. In the event that Pinger discovers that it has received personal information from a child under the age of 13, Pinger will promptly delete such personal information in a secure manner.

**Information Pinger Collects and Uses**

Pinger collects information when you use and access Pinger’s products, services and website. We categorize the information we collect into three categories (collectively referred to as “Customer Information”): Personal Information, App Data and Share Data.

“Personal Information” is information about you that is personally identifiable, including your full name, business or residential address, email address, land-line or existing mobile phone number, or billing information.

“App Data” is information about the nature of your usage of Pinger’s website and products and services and non-personal information. App Data can include: IP addresses, domain servers, referring/exit pages, operating system

information, unique device identifiers, such as UDID and/or Ethernet MAC address, date/time stamp, clickstream data and information about actions taken by you through interaction with Pinger’s products and/or advertising displayed within Pinger products, messages sent and received using Pinger services, information about those messages (date, duration, recipients, size, attachments), type of device, location information, age, gender, type of web browser, one or more cookies that identify your browser, and telecommunications carrier information.

“Share Data” is data and information you provide for use with Pinger’s products or services, such as text, audio, video and photos you make available through the Apps or contacts you add or import for use with Pinger products, and which may be made available to third parties by your actions when using Pinger products or services.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Pinger uses Customer Information to enhance your use of the Pinger services by processing such information for various purposes, including improving and providing Pinger’s products and services, product notifications, delivering advertisements and related links, for sending, sharing and storing your Share Data as you direct through use of Pinger products and services, and other purposes relating to offering you Pinger products and services.

If you provide your phone number as part of a request for information about Pinger products or services or in setting up an account, we may use that phone number and share that phone number with third parties to contact you about Pinger products and services and to provide advertisements to you about Pinger Products and services.

**Pinger does not rent, sell, or share any Customer Information except as provided above and unless: you initiate the sharing through the Pinger products, services or website; you have provided your express consent; and in the following circumstances:**

(i) Pinger may engage a trusted third party to perform limited functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling newsletter subscriptions, sending requested postal mail and e-mail, SMS, MMS, and voice communications, analyzing and processing data (such as billing information), and providing customer service. We require that these parties agree to use such information in a confidential manner. These third parties may have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions, but we do not permit them to use it for other purposes.

(ii) Pinger may share App Data and certain aggregated, non-personal information with third parties, but such information does not include your name, email address or any other Personal Information.

(iii) Pinger may share Customer Information to respond to legal requirements, when legally required to do so, or at the request of governmental authorities.

(iv) Pinger may share Customer Information to verify or enforce compliance with user agreements and applicable laws, to protect against fraud, to detect and prevent security or technical issues, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Pinger products, services, computing systems, or website, or to protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Pinger, its subscribers or the public.

(v) Pinger may share Customer Information with a successor entity or in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate reorganization provided that use of Customer Information is in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

(vi) Pinger may share your Customer Information with a third party if you have consented to receive information from that third party through Pinger products or services. Such third parties will handle, store, retain and access such user information in accordance with the terms and conditions of their agreements with you, if any, as well as their own privacy policies and as authorized and agreed upon by you as part of agreements for use of our products and services. It is your responsibility to carefully review such agreements and

privacy policies. You acknowledge that Pinger shall have no liability to you for sharing of such information to such third parties as authorized by you and Pinger disclaims any and all liability relating thereto. If Pinger desires to use Personal Information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy, we will offer you the opportunity to opt out of such use for those other purposes.

**Cookies and Tracking**

When you visit Pinger or use Pinger applications, we may send cookies to your computer that uniquely identify your browser or use tracking pixels, agents or other visitor identification technology (collectively, “Tags”) that collect App Data. We may also include Tags in promotional materials in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

We use and share App Data as provided above.

Most browsers allow you to disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to utilize certain Pinger products and services.

We use analytics tools provided by Google, Facebook, Flurry, adjust, braze and Crashlytics (“Analytics Tools”) which also use Tags to collect and analyze information about your use of our desktop and mobile applications. We use Analytics Tools to collect App Data, which we use as provided above. That information is also used by the Analytics Tools providers according to their privacy policies.

In some Apps we use Google Signals, which is an extension to Google Analytics. If you have enabled personalized ads in your Google account, then Google Signals allows us access to data linked to your Google account for advertising reports, remarketing, cross-device reporting, and interest and demographic reports, and to use that data for cross-device remarketing.

You can find more details about how Google uses data it collects here: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). Some applications may use Google Contacts API to allow access to your contacts using [https://www.googleapis.com/auth/contacts](https://www.googleapis.com/auth/contacts). That information is stored on your device and not uploaded to our servers, and is used solely to allow you to communicate with contacts using the features of those applications. For more, see [https://console.cloud.google.com](https://console.cloud.google.com/) and [https://console.cloud.google.com/tos?id=universal](https://console.cloud.google.com/tos?id=universal). To learn how Flurry collects, uses, and stores such information, see the Flurry privacy policy at [https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/index.htm](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/index.htm). You may choose to opt out of the Flurry services via the Flurry Opt-Out Page, available at [https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do](https://dev.flurry.com/secure/optOut.do). To learn more about data collection with Facebook Analytics, see [https://developers.facebook.com/docs/analytics/overview](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/analytics/overview). To learn more about how braze uses data it collects, see [https://www.braze.com/terms/](https://www.braze.com/terms/). Crashlytics privacy policy can be found at [http://try.crashlytics.com/terms/privacy-policy.pdf](http://try.crashlytics.com/terms/privacy-policy.pdf). To opt out of Google Analytics and Google Signals, see [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

You hereby expressly consent that we are entitled to: (i) place Tags for the above-mentioned uses on your computer or device and to use the information gathered from Tags as provided in this Privacy Policy; and (ii) utilize information first party information and information provided by third parties for personalization and cross-device remarketing.

Currently, we do not respond to “Do Not Track” browser features.

**Security and Data Integrity**

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Customer Information under our control. Customer Information we collect is stored in a secure manner that is accessible only by authorized Pinger personnel, contractors, and agents bound by confidentiality obligations and is only disclosed under the provisions of this Privacy Policy. Our processing of Personal Information is only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Periodically, Pinger undertakes a review of its privacy practices to ensure that that the information we collect is needed to provide or improve the services we provide.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

As a convenience to you, we may provide links and/or connections to third-party web sites or services from within our website or our products or services. Pinger is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third-party sites.

**Access/Removal of Your Personal Information**

If you want us to remove your Personal Information from our database, or would like to access the Personal Information we have that was collected from you, you can contact us using the contact information provided below. Certain of our products and services require the use of App Data and such data is retained by Pinger and used as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Modifications of Privacy Policy**

Pinger reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such change, update or modification on the Pinger website and in the app stores from which Apps are made available. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon notice, which Pinger may provide by any means, including, without limitation, posting on the Pinger website, notifications within Pinger applications, or electronic mail. Your continued use of the Pinger website and/or any Pinger products and services following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes. Use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please send us an email at [info@pinger.com](mailto:info@pinger.com) or write to us at Pinger, Inc. 97 S. 2nd St, Ste. 210, San Jose, CA 95113. If we receive formal privacy-related complaints, it is our policy to use reasonable efforts to communicate with the complaining party about its concerns to resolve privacy complaints.

**Interest-Based Advertiser Opt Outs**

Pinger is not a member of any self-regulatory bodies for interest-based advertising like the DAA and NAI, but some of our advertisers and advertising services providers are members of self-regulatory bodies and require that we provide you with the following out links to the NAI and DAA opt out programs: for the NAI, see [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices), and for the DAA, see [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Last updated October 11, 2023

**Privacy**

Privacy Notice

SOME USEFUL DATA PRIVACY FACTS FROM YOUR FRIENDS AT PINGER

We’ve provided this Privacy Notice to help you understand how Pinger, Inc. (“Pinger,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) collects and uses personal information and, for California residents, to inform them of the categories of personal information we collect and the purposes for which the categories of personal information will be used, as required under the California Consumer Privacy Act, as augmented by the California Privacy Rights Act (collectively, “CCPA”) and other relevant privacy laws.

The technologies we use process data for our products and services are complicated, but this Privacy Notice is meant to provide you with an easy-to-understand overview of the categories of personal information we collect, why we collect them, and how we use them. While this Privacy Notice provides a general overview, for a complete understanding about what personal information we gather and how we use it, please review our [Privacy Policy](https://www.pinger.com/privacy-policy/) and [Terms of Service](https://www.pinger.com/privacy-policy/terms-and-conditions/). Also, please review our “Notice of Financial Incentive” included below.

What does Pinger do?

Pinger offers software applications for iOS and Android mobile devices (and limited versions of those applications for internet-connected desktop computers), that enable end users to send SMS and MMS communications as well as to place or receive calls. Pinger licenses its applications to U.S.-based end users for use in the U.S. Pinger’s Canadian subsidiary, Dinopilot, offers the some of the same applications and functionality in limited markets outside of the U.S. If you’re an end user licensed by Dinopilot, references to “Pinger,” “we,” “us,” or “our” in this Privacy Notice mean Dinopilot.

Pinger’s mobile applications are: “Pinger,” “TextFree,” “TextFree Voice,” “Sideline”, and “Index” (collectively, the “Apps”). The Apps are available in iOS and/or Android versions for tablets and smartphones and are distributed through Apple’s “App Store” and the “Google Play” store (collectively, “App Stores”). Pinger, TextFree and TextFree Voice (collectively, “TextFree Apps”) are supported by advertising revenue and are free to use, with certain additional features, including an advertising-free feature, available for purchase as part of our TextFree Plus subscription. Sideline and Index require a paid subscription but may include promotional placements.

TextFree Apps provide end users with access to a Pinger-supplied phone number that becomes associated with an end user’s account. Receiving and sending SMS and MMS messages through the TextFree Apps are free to users as are inbound calls. However, placing outbound calls requires end users to either purchase license credits for outbound calling through App Stores, or earn license credits for outbound calling by viewing video ads (each ad view typically equates to one minute of license credits) or completing third party offers.

Sideline is a subscription-based, communications software platform intended for individuals. Specifically, Sideline provides phone numbers, voicemail, voicemail to text, inbound call routing functionality, multi-device call notification, text messaging, and telephone number management. Sideline provides its subscribers with communications tools to leverage their own devices and wireless plans.

Index is a subscription-based software platform intended for small businesses. Specifically, Index provides text-based tools such as booking appointments, sending invoices, collecting payments, and getting reviews. In addition, Index also provides phone numbers, voicemail, voicemail to text, inbound call routing functionality, multi-device call notification, text messaging, and telephone number management.

Sideline and Index may include promotional offers which may require that you allow use of your personal information. That information is only shared if you decide to pursue the offer, but you can opt out of receiving those offers by changing your “Content Preferences” through the “Settings” of the applicable App.

**What personal information does Pinger need to use?**

In order for inbound or outbound calls and messages to work for our Sideline, Index, and TextFree Apps, we need basic information about the sender and the recipient, namely their phone numbers. We also need to know how to associate all those calls and messages with a specific account for those Apps, so we require you to provide some basic information during signup. That’s how we can make sure that calls and messages are connected correctly. That information is required in order for us to provide our services, so please keep that in mind when deciding whether to use our Apps.

Since our TextFree Apps are supported by advertising, we -like other ad-supported companies (e.g. Facebook) – gather information about you, your mobile device from the TextFree Apps, and your use of TextFree Apps. That information is shared with Advertising Companies who process it and match it with other data and use algorithms to serve ads that are more relevant to you. That’s basically how we, and others, make money to support and offer TextFree Apps for free. Please keep in mind that some of that information, such as specific geo-location information, passes to Advertising Companies and may not be retained by us.

**Can I opt out of the sale of my personal information?**

Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), provision of personal information to our advertising service providers may constitute a “sale” of that information, so for CCPA purposes, we consider that we “sell” your personal information to deliver ads in our TextFree Apps. If you don’t like that personal information is used to deliver ads to you in our TextFree Apps, then you can opt out by purchasing a TextFree Plus subscription from the applicable Apps Stores. For Sideline and Index, you can always opt out of receiving promotional offers and other content by going to your app settings and turning off content notifications.

**NOTICE OF FINANCIAL INCENTIVE:** If you’re a California resident, you should know that the TextFree Plus subscription is offered in compliance with Section 1798.125(a)(2) of the CCPA which allows us to charge a fee if we can’t generate any advertising revenue from your use of the TextFree Apps. That fee is a good faith estimate of the value of the advertising revenue for a typical user of the TextFree Apps as determined by an industry standard calculation of lifetime value of a user who views our ads as compared to the lifetime value of a typical user who purchases TextFree Plus.

When you purchase a TextFree Plus subscription, we don’t provide your personal information to Advertising Companies, but you have to maintain that subscription in order to continue using TextFree Plus because other versions of TextFree use your personal information for advertising purposes. If you wish to cancel your TextFree Plus subscription as a financial incentive to not have your personal information used for advertising, you will have to do so from the Apple or Google Play store. If you cancel or let the TextFree Plus subscription lapse, then your personal information will be used for advertising in the TextFree Apps and, by allowing the subscription to lapse, you are expressly consenting to our use of your personal information for advertising within the TextFree Apps.

**What categories of third parties does Pinger engage?**

While Pinger maintains its own data servers for the core data management for the Apps, we engage third parties to provide other services, as follows: (i) .”Backend Providers” provide the backend transmission systems necessary for the Apps to function and include local exchange carriers connected to the PSTN (Public Switch Telephone Network) who connect communications for us, data backhaul providers who transfer data across the continent, and hosting providers; (ii) “Service Providers” who provide analytics, calendar, user notification, and related business services and customer support platforms; and (iii) “Advertising Companies” who provide advertising services for our TextFree Apps. We have contractual agreements with those third parties that limit the use of personal information we control for the specific purpose identified in those agreements.

**What categories of personal information does Pinger collect?**

Some data we collect from our Apps and our websites at textfree.us, Pinger.com, Sideline.com, and Getindex.com (collectively, the “Site”) is “personal information” under the CCPA because it identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device. Currently, we collect this information from you and your device. Since paid features of our Apps are purchased through App Stores, we don’t collect any financial information from you, but we do collect other categories of personal information.

_Please note that as a company in the communications space, we receive regular requests from law enforcement and governmental authorities investigating wrongdoing or illegal activity and, accordingly, we retain specific information for longer periods, in part to honor the needs of law enforcement and governmental authorities._

Below is a summary of the categories of personal information we may have collected from consumers within the last twelve (12) months and the main purpose for its collection. Please note that we only collect personal information from you when you use our Apps, the Site or interact with our customer support personnel. Also, not all the information identified below is collected from every end user and not all information is personal to the user or is associated with a specific user.

| Category | Examples | General Business  <br>Purpose | Duration of Retention |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Registration  <br>Information | * Email<br>* Name<br>* Phone Number<br>* Password<br>* Mobile Carrier Identifier<br>* IP address for Registration | To provide our services, to provide advertising for our Apps that support advertising, and to comply with legal requests | Indefinitely |
| Identifiers | * Advertising and vendor identifiers<br>* iOS identifiers<br>* Google ID<br>* International mobile equipment identity (IMEI)<br>* Device identifiers | To provide our services, to provide advertising for our Apps that support advertising, and to comply with legal requests | Indefinitely |
| Location information | * Geo location of your device if you have given the app permission to collect your location information | To provide our services and for advertisers to provide advertising for our Apps that support advertising | Not retained |
| Network information | * IP address for network activity<br>* MCC and MNC information<br>* Local Wi-Fi Identifier | To provide our services and to provide advertising for our TextFree Apps, and to comply with legal requests | 2 years account activity  <br>Local Wi-Fi (90 days) |
| Survey information | * Survey answers<br>* Information provided as part of the Survey | To learn more about our customers and contact them, and to improve our Apps and services | Indefinitely, but not maintained in a manner that allows for easily searchable and identifiable personal data |
| Message Content | * Text messages you send and receive<br>* Voicemails | To provide our services and to comply with legal requests | Indefinitely for active account and 6 months for inactive accounts, with automated implementation of this process to be completed in Q1 of 2024 |
| Account Attributes | * Audience segmentation<br>* Promotional offers to certain audiences | To provide advertising and promotional placements | Indefinitely for active account and 6 months for inactive accounts, with automated implementation of this process to be completed in Q2 of 2024 |
| App Usage Information | * App features used and pages viewed (although not identified to an individual)<br>* Purchasing activity, such as if a subscription was purchased, but without any personal financial information retained | App usage information is retained to improve our services | 2 years for App feature usage and 45 days for purchasing activity data |
| Call Detail Records | * The time, duration and phone numbers of text messages and calls | To provide our Services and for legal compliance | 2 years |
| Contacts | * The contacts associated with your account | To provide our Services | As long as the account is open |

We disclose your personal information to Back End Providers to enable communications transmissions for our Apps. We disclose your personal information to Services Providers to provide customer support, to analyze the usage of our Apps and the Site, and to initiate App alerts. And we disclose your personal information to Advertising Companies to serve ads to our TextFree Apps.

We will not collect additional categories of personal information from you or use it differently than as described unless we provide you with advance notice and obtain your consent.

**What about personal information from users under the age of 16?**

Where users of our TextFree Apps have indicated that they are under the age of 16, we don’t sell their personal information and their account is terminated.

**What are other uses of personal information?**

As noted above, we use personal information to provide our services. In addition, we may use or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:

To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided. For example, if you contact our customer support, we may use your email address to communicate with you about your support issue:

* To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
* To provide you with alerts and other notices concerning our products or services.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights under the Apps’ Terms of Service.
* For testing, research, analysis and product development to improve our Apps and Site.
* To protect the rights, property or safety of us, our subscribers or others and to respond to legal requests.
* As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the CCPA.
* For the other purposes set forth in our Privacy Policy.

**Where is the data held?**

Pinger utilizes data centers in the United States, where all of our necessary systems are located. Some of our support programs leverage affiliated companies in the European Union (EU) to provide customer support, and those European-based customer support teams may have remote access to account information, but they do not store that information. Transfers of personal data to and among our affiliates are subject to terms of intercompany agreements governing the transfer of data to the United States and protection of that data under applicable law. Also, we require that you acknowledge and agree to allow us to transfer data to the United States, so if you’re not willing to provide that consent, you shouldn’t use our products and services.

**What safeguards does Pinger utilize to protect data?**

We take appropriate technical and organizational measures for our systems to comply with data privacy to ensure a level of data protection appropriate to the risk resulting from the processing of personal data, taking into account the state of the art, the costs of implementation and the nature, scope, context and purposes of processing, as well as the severity and likelihood of realization of risks for the rights and freedoms of folks who’ve provided the data.

**Is Pinger a “controller” or a “processor”?**

Lots of companies are making distinctions between who is a “controller,” and who is a “processor,” when it comes to using personal data. That’s because the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) distinguishes a “controller,” (the party primarily responsible for protecting “personal data”) from a “processor” (which is essentially a subcontractor that has secondary, but important responsibilities to protect “personal data”). In the context of providing services to you, Pinger would be considered a “controller” if GDPR were to apply. However, currently you are not allowed to use our applications in the EU.

**What are my rights as a California resident?**

The CCPA provides California residents with specific rights regarding their personal information, as described below.

_Opt Out of the Sale of Personal Information_

The CCPA requires that we notify you of your right to opt out of the sale of your personal information. As noted above, for our Sideline and Index mobile applications, we don’t sell your personal information as contemplated under the CCPA, so there’s no need for you to opt out of the sale of your personal information for those Apps.

For our TextFree Apps, as noted above you can opt out of the sale of personal information by purchasing a TextFree Plus subscription, subject to the conditions noted above.

_Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights_

You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Note that you may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you:

* The categories of personal information we collected about you.
* The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
* Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information.
* The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you (also called a data portability request).
* If we sold or disclosed your personal information for a business purpose:
    * The categories of personal information that we’ve sold about you and the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold.
    * The categories of personal information that we disclosed for a business purpose.

For TextFree, TextFree Voice, and Pinger users looking for more information about how to contact us to provide you with an information request, click on this link: [Send Me Specifics About My Personal Information](https://messages.textfree.us/login?privacy=ccpa).

You can also request this information via [TFPrivacy@pinger.com](mailto:TFPrivacy@pinger.com).

For Sideline users looking for more information about how to contact us to provide you with an information request, click on this link: [Send Me Specifics About My Personal Information](https://messages.sideline.com/#/login?privacy=ccpa).

For Sideline or Index users looking for more information about how to contact us to provide you with an information request, click on this link for Sideline: [Send Me Specifics About My Personal Information](https://messages.sideline.com/login?privacy=ccpa) and this link for Index: [Send Me Specifics About My Personal Information](https://app.getindex.com/login?privacy=ccpa)

You can also request this information via [SLPrivacy@sideline.com](mailto:SLPrivacy@sideline.com) or [Privacy@getindex.com](mailto:Privacy@getindex.com).

_Deletion Request Rights_

You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions.

As discussed above, we can’t provide any services to you without your personal information, so if you ask us to delete your personal information, we will have to terminate your account and you will no longer be able to use the Apps for their intended purpose.

If you still want us to delete your personal information, you have to send us a verified request for us to do so. As with information requests, the only way for us to verify who you are is for you to log in and contact us using our Apps. TextFree, TextFree Voice, and Pinger users click on this link for how to contact us for deletion requests: [Delete My Data](https://messages.textfree.us/login?privacy=ccpa). Sideline users click on this link for how to contact us for deletion requests: [Delete My Data](https://messages.sideline.com/login?privacy=ccpa). Index users click on this link for how to contact us for deletion requests: [Delete My Data](https://app.getindex.com/login?privacy=ccpa).

Please note that the CCPA includes a number of exceptions that allow us to retain your personal data despite your deletion request, so we may retain your personal data under those exceptions.

**Why do I have to log in and contact you to make CCPA requests?**

As noted above, since we don’t require a lot of information for you to use our Apps, and since we may not verify the accuracy of the personal information you provide, we may not have sufficient data to verify who you are unless you log in and contact us using our Apps or provide us with the requested information. If you log in and contact us using our Apps, we can associate your request with a specific account and then take action on your request.

**What do I do if I have concerns about the use of my data?**

If you have concerns about the use of your data, contact us at [privacy@pinger.com](mailto:privacy@pinger.com). Please review our [Privacy Policy](https://pinger.com/privacy-policy/) for specific details about what is required of you when you contact us. And please remember that the choice to use our products is entirely yours: if you’re not comfortable with letting us use personal information as described in this Privacy Notice, in our [Privacy Policy](https://pingerdev.wpengine.com/privacy-policy/), and in our [Terms of Service](https://pingerdev.wpengine.com/privacy-policy/end-user-terms/#terms), then please don’t download our Apps.

Last Updated: August 10, 2023

**Privacy**

Data Protection Policy - International

Overview

This Data Protection Policy describes how Pinger treats data, including personal data, which it collects and receives related to your use of Pinger’s products, services, and websites.

Information Pinger Collects and Uses

Pinger collects data when you use and access Pinger’s products, services and websites. The information collected includes Personal Data, App Data, Traffic Data and Share Data (collectively, “Customer Information”). “Personal Data” is information provided by you which can be used to directly identify you, like your full name, address, email address, billing information, home phone number, and home and business addresses. No Personal Data is collected when you merely access the public areas of our websites. “App Data” is information about the nature of your usage of Pinger’s websites and products and services and non-personal demographic information. App Data includes: IP addresses, domain servers, referring/exit pages, operating system information, type of web browser, date/time stamp, and clickstream data; and for Pinger products and services App Data also includes device identifiers, messages sent and received using Pinger services, information about those messages, type of device, location information, user age and gender demographics, browser type, carrier information, and information and statistics about use of Pinger product features. “Share Data” is data you provide for use with Pinger’s products or services and which may be made available to third parties by your actions when using Pinger products or services.

**Use and Processing of Information; Sharing and Disclosure**

Pinger uses and processes Customer Information to provide, improve and modify Pinger products and services, to authenticate users, to provide customer service and support, to communicate with users through Pinger products and services, to publish and provide advertising through our products and services, for Pinger product notifications, for fraud detection and compliance with user agreements, and for sending, sharing and storing your Share Data as you direct through use of Pinger products and services. Pinger processes Customer Information, including Personal Data, on our servers in the United States of America and additional countries where we may add servers.  In some cases, we may process Customer Information on behalf of, through, or according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners, but only when you have provided your express, informed and revocable consent to allow us to do so.

Pinger does not rent, sell, or share any Customer Information unless we have your express informed consent and in the following circumstances:

(i) Pinger may engage a trusted third party to perform limited functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling newsletter subscriptions, sending and receiving requested postal mail, e-mail, SMS, MMS, and voice communications, analyzing and processing data (such as billing information) and ad serving, and providing customer service. We require that these parties agree to use such information in a confidential manner and in compliance with this Data Protection Policy. These third parties may have access to Personal Data needed to perform their functions, but we do not permit them to use it for other purposes without your consent except as required by applicable law.

(ii) Pinger may share with third parties App Data and non-personal information which does not identify you individually.

(iii) Pinger may share Customer Information to respond to legal requirements, when legally required to do so, and at the request of governmental authorities.

(iv) Pinger may share Customer Information to verify or enforce compliance with user agreements and applicable laws, to protect against fraud, to detect and prevent security or technical issues, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Pinger products, services, computing systems, or websites, or to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Pinger, its subscribers or the public.

(v) Pinger may share Customer Information with a successor entity or in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate reorganization provided that use of Customer Information is in compliance with this Data Protection Policy.

(vi) Pinger may share Customer Information with a third party if you have consented to receive information from, or share it with, that third party through Pinger products or services. Such third parties will handle, store, retain and access such Customer Information in accordance with the terms and conditions of their agreements with you, if any, as well as their own data protection policies. It is your responsibility to carefully review such agreements and data protection policies. You acknowledge that Pinger shall have no liability to you for sharing of such information to such third parties and Pinger disclaims any and all liability relating thereto.

(vii) In order to provide software and services to you, Pinger may share Customer Information with its parent and/or subsidiary companies within and without the European Union and those parties may process and store Customer Information in any country in the world subject to this Data Protection Policy.

**Cookies**

When you visit Pinger, we may send cookies to your computer that uniquely identify your browser or use pixel tags (sometimes referred to as web beacons) to record pages visited. We use cookies and tags to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking usage information. Most browsers allow you to disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. We may also include tags in promotional materials in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. You hereby expressly consent that Pinger is entitled to place these cookies and tags for the above-mentioned services on your computer or device. If you disable cookies, you may not be able to utilize certain Pinger products and services.

Traffic data  

Telecommunications traffic data (“Traffic Data”) is collected in connection with your use of the Pinger services and is stored after the end of the communication for billing purposes up to the maximum periods authorized by applicable law and will be deleted thereafter, unless (i) you have raised objections against the billing, or (ii) if there is a reasonable suspicion of fraud or of other criminal activity. For the purposes of law enforcement, Traffic Data is also stored in compliance with applicable law for data retention. Traffic Data stored pursuant to this second sentence cannot be used by you for the purposes of a billing dispute.

**Security and Data Integrity**

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Customer Information under our control. Customer Information we collect is stored in a secure manner that is accessible only by authorized Pinger personnel, contractors, and agents bound by confidentiality obligations and is only disclosed under the provisions of this Data Protection Policy. Our processing of Personal Data is only for the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise in accordance with this Data Protection Policy and applicable EU and national data protection laws. Periodically, Pinger undertakes a review of its privacy practices to ensure that that the information we collect is needed to provide or improve the services we provide.

Children’s Personal Information  

The Pinger websites comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). Pinger does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13 through the Pinger websites. In addition, in the event that a user identifies himself or herself as a child under the age of 13 within the Pinger websites, Pinger will not collect, store or use any Personal Data of such user. Further, in the event that Pinger receives Personal Data that Pinger discovers was provided by a child under the age of 13, Pinger will promptly delete such Personal Data in a secure manner.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

As a convenience to you, we may provide links and/or connections to third-party web sites or services from within our websites or our products or services. Pinger is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these third-party sites.

**Access/Removal of Your Personal Information**

If you want us to remove your Personal Data from our database, or would like to access the Personal Data that was collected from you, you can contact us using the contact information provided below. Upon termination of the Pinger services, your Personal Data will be deleted. Certain of our products and services require the use of App Data and such data is retained by Pinger and used as described in this Data Protection Policy and in end user agreements for the applicable products and services.

**Modifications of Data Protection Policy**

Pinger reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, update or modify this Data Protection Policy at any time by posting such change, update or modification on the Pinger websites, which will be effective immediately upon notice, which Pinger may provide by any means, including, without limitation, posting on the Pinger websites, notifications within Pinger applications, or electronic mail. Your continued use of the Pinger websites and/or any Pinger products and services following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes. Use of information that we gather is subject to the Data Protection Policy in effect at the time of use.

Contact Us  

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Data Protection Policy, such as what Personal Data is stored about you, please send us an email at [info@pinger.com](mailto:info@pinger.com). If we receive formal privacy-related complaints, it is our policy to use reasonable efforts to communicate with the complaining party about its concerns to resolve privacy complaints. For the purposes of this Data Protection Policy, “Pinger” shall mean either Pinger (UK) Ltd. or Pinger International Ltd., depending upon which entity’s user agreement you have accepted.

Last updated March 1, 2012  

Übersicht

Diese Datenschutzrichtlinie enthält Informationen dazu, wie Pinger Daten, einschließlich persönlicher Daten, die das Unternehmen erfasst und durch Ihre Nutzung von Produkten, Dienstleistungen und Websites von Pinger erhält, behandelt.

Informationen, die von Pinger erfasst und verwendet werden

Pinger sammelt Daten, wenn Sie Produkte, Dienstleistungen und Websites von Pinger nutzen und auf diese zugreifen. Zu den erfassten Informationen gehören persönliche Daten, App-Daten, Datenverkehrsinformationen und freigegebene Daten (zusammen „Kundeninformationen“). „Persönliche Daten“ sind von Ihnen bereitgestellte Daten, die zu Ihrer direkten Identifizierung verwendet werden können, z. B. vollständiger Name, Adresse, E-Mail-Adresse, Rechnungsinformationen, private Telefonnummer sowie Privat- und Dienstanschriften. Es werden keine persönlichen Daten erfasst, wenn Sie nur auf die öffentlichen Bereiche unserer Websites zugreifen. „App-Daten“ sind Informationen in Bezug auf die Art Ihrer Nutzung von Websites, Produkten und Dienstleistungen von Pinger sowie nicht-persönliche demografische Informationen. Zu App-Daten gehören: IP-Adressen, Domain-Server, weiterleitende/Exit-Seiten, Informationen zum Betriebssystem, Art des Webbrowsers, Datums-/Uhrzeitangaben und Clickstream-Daten. Für Pinger-Produkte und -Dienstleistungen umfassen App-Daten ebenfalls Gerätekennung, mithilfe von Pinger-Diensten gesendete und empfangene Nachrichten, Informationen über diese Nachrichten, Art des Geräts, Standortangaben, Alter des Nutzers und Geschlechtsangaben, Art des Browsers, Anbieterinformationen sowie Informationen und Statistiken zur Verwendung von Pinger-Produktfunktionen. „Freigegebene Daten“ sind Daten, die Sie zur Verwendung von Pinger-Produkten oder -Dienstleistungen bereitstellen und die Sie mit Ihren Aktivitäten bei der Nutzung von Pinger-Produkten oder -Dienstleistungen Drittparteien zur Verfügung stellen können.

**Nutzung und Verarbeitung von Informationen; Freigabe und Offenlegung**

Pinger verwendet und verarbeitet Kundeninformationen, um Produkte und Dienstleistungen von Pinger anzubieten, zu verbessern und zu modifizieren, um die Identität von Nutzern zu bestätigen, um Kundendienste und Support bereitzustellen, um mit Nutzern über Pinger-Produkte und -Dienstleistungen zu kommunizieren, um Werbung mithilfe unserer Produkte und Dienstleistungen zu veröffentlichen und bereitzustellen, zu Benachrichtigungen über Pinger-Produkte, zur Feststellung von Betrug und zur Einhaltung von Nutzungsbedingungen sowie zum Senden, Freigeben und Speichern Ihrer Daten entsprechend Ihren Anweisungen, die Sie durch die Verwendung von Pinger-Produkten und -Dienstleistungen gegeben haben. Pinger verarbeitet die Kundeninformationen, einschließlich der persönlichen Daten, auf unseren Servern in den Vereinigten Staaten von Amerika und weiteren Ländern, in denen wir möglicherweise weitere Server hinzufügen. In einigen Fällen können wir Kundeninformationen im Auftrag, mittels oder entsprechend den Anweisungen einer Drittpartei, wie z. B. einem unserer Werbepartner, verarbeiten, jedoch nur, wenn Sie uns dies mit Ihrer ausdrücklichen, informierten und wiederrufbaren Einwilligung gestatten.

Pinger vermietet oder verkauft keine Kundeninformationen und gibt diese nicht frei, es sei denn, wir haben Ihre ausdrückliche Einverständniserklärung erhalten, und es treffen folgende Umstände zu:

(i) Pinger kann eine vertrauenswürdige Drittpartei beauftragen, beschränkte Aufgaben in unserem Namen durchzuführen, z. B. die Erfüllung von Rundbrief-Abonnements, das Senden oder Empfangen von Post, E-Mails, SMS, MMS und Sprachmitteilungen, Analyse und Verarbeitung von Daten (wie z. B. Rechnungsinformationen), Werbedienste und Bereitstellung von Kundendienstleistungen. Wir verlangen, dass diese Parteien zustimmen, solche Informationen auf vertrauliche Weise und in Einklang mit dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie zu behandeln. Diese Drittparteien können Zugang zu persönlichen Daten, die zur Durchführung ihrer Aufgaben notwendig sind, erhalten. Wir gestatten ihnen jedoch nicht, diese ohne Ihre Zustimmung zu anderen Zwecken zu verwenden, sofern nicht vom geltenden Gesetz erfordert.

(ii) Pinger kann Drittparteien App-Daten und nicht-persönliche Informationen freigeben, mit denen Ihre Identität nicht identifiziert werden kann.

(iii) Pinger kann Kundeninformationen freigeben, um rechtlichen Anforderungen nachzukommen, wenn dies gesetzlich gefordert ist, sowie auf Verlangen von Regierungsbehörden.

(iv) Pinger kann Kundeninformationen freigeben, um die Einhaltung der Nutzungsbedingungen und geltenden Gesetze zu bestätigen und durchzusetzen, um sich gegen Betrug zu schützen, um Sicherheits- oder technische Probleme aufzudecken und zu verhindern, um sich vor Missbrauch und unbefugter Nutzung von Pinger-Produkten, -Dienstleistungen, -Rechnersystemen oder -Websites zu schützen, oder um sich vor der Verletzung der Rechte, des Eigentums oder der Sicherheit von Pinger, seinen Nutzern oder der Öffentlichkeit zu schützen.

(v) Pinger kann Kundeninformationen an ein Nachfolgeunternehmen oder in Verbindung mit einer Unternehmensfusion, Konzernbildung, dem Verkauf von Vermögenswerten oder anderen Neuorganisationen des Unternehmens freigeben, vorausgesetzt, dass die Verwendung der Kundeninformationen im Einklang mit dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie erfolgt.

(vi) Pinger kann Kundeninformationen an eine Drittpartei weitergeben, wenn Sie dem Erhalt oder der Freigabe von Informationen von dieser bzw. an diese Drittpartei durch Pinger-Produkte oder -Dienstleistungen zugestimmt haben. Derartige Drittparteien werden solche Kundeninformationen im Einklang mit den Geschäftsbedingungen ihrer ggf. mit Ihnen bestehenden Verträge bzw. im Einklang mit ihren eigenen Datenschutzrichtlinien behandeln, speichern, aufbewahren und auf sie zugreifen. Sie sind dafür verantwortlich, solche Verträge und Datenschutzrichtlinien sorgfältig zu prüfen. Sie bestätigen hiermit, dass Pinger Ihnen gegenüber nicht für die Freigabe solcher Informationen an derartige Drittparteien haftet und Pinger schließt sämtliche Haftungen diesbezüglich aus.

(vii) Um Ihnen Software und Dienstleistungen bereitzustellen, kann Pinger Kundeninformationen an seine Mutter- und/oder Tochterunternehmen innerhalb und außerhalb der Europäischen Union weitergeben und diese Parteien können die Kundeninformationen in jedem Land der Welt, solange es dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie unterliegt, verarbeiten und speichern.

**Cookies**

Wenn Sie Pinger besuchen, können wir Ihrem Computer Cookies senden, mit denen Ihr Browser eindeutig identifiziert wird, oder Pixel-Tags verwenden (die mitunter als Web-Beacons bezeichnet werden), um die besuchten Seiten aufzuzeichnen. Wir setzen Cookies und Tags ein, um die Qualität unserer Dienste durch die Speicherung von Nutzerpräferenzen und Tracking der Nutzungsinformationen zu verbessern. Bei den meisten Browsern ist es möglich, Cookies zu deaktivieren. Sie können Ihren Browser auch so einstellen, dass Sie eine Warnung erhalten, wenn Cookies an Ihren Computer gesendet werden. Wir können auch Tags in Werbematerialien einfügen, um festzustellen, ob Nachrichten geöffnet wurden und auf sie reagiert wurde. Hiermit erklären Sie sich ausdrücklich damit einverstanden, dass Pinger berechtigt ist, diese Cookies und Tags für die oben genannten Leistungen auf Ihrem Computer oder Gerät zu platzieren. Sollten Sie die Cookies deaktivieren, werden Sie möglicherweise nicht in der Lage sein, gewisse Produkte und Dienstleistungen von Pinger zu nutzen.

Datenverkehrsinformationen  

Datenverkehrsinformationen im Telekommunikationsbereich („Datenverkehrsinformationen“) werden in Verbindung mit Ihrer Nutzung von Pinger-Dienstleistungen erfasst und am Ende der Kommunikation zu Rechnungszwecken für den nach geltendem Gesetz zulässigen maximalen Zeitraum gespeichert. Im Anschluss daran werden sie gelöscht, es sei denn (i) Sie haben Einwände gegen die Rechnung erhoben oder (ii) es besteht ein angemessener Verdacht auf Betrug oder andere kriminelle Handlungen. Zum Zweck des Gesetzesvollzugs werden Datenverkehrsinformationen auch in Einhaltung der geltenden Gesetze zur Datenspeicherung gespeichert. Datenverkehrsinformationen, die gemäß letzterem Satz gespeichert werden, können von Ihnen nicht zum Zweck eines Rechnungskonflikts verwendet werden.

**Sicherheit und Datenintegrität**

Wir verfügen über physische, elektronische und verfahrenstechnische Schutzmaßnahmen, um uns gegen Verlust, Missbrauch und Änderungen der sich in unserer Kontrolle befindlichen Kundeninformationen zu schützen. Die von uns erfassten Kundeninformationen werden auf sichere Weise gespeichert und sind nur befugtem Personal, Vertragspartnern und Beauftragten von Pinger zugänglich, die durch Vertraulichkeitsverpflichtungen gebunden sind. Sie können nur nach den Bestimmungen dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie offengelegt werden. Unsere Verarbeitung persönlicher Daten erfolgt nur zu dem Zweck, zu dem sie erfasst wurden, oder anderweitig im Einklang mit dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie und geltenden EU- und nationalen Datenschutzgesetzen. Pinger überprüft seine Datenschutzpraktiken regelmäßig, um zu gewährleisten, dass die von uns erfassten Informationen zur Bereitstellung oder Verbesserung der von uns gebotenen Dienstleistungen notwendig sind.

Persönliche Informationen von Kindern  

Die Pinger-Websites halten das „Gesetz zum Schutz der Privatsphäre von Kindern im Internet“ (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, „COPPA“) ein. Pinger nimmt keine wissentliche Erfassung persönlicher Daten von Kindern unter 13 Jahren über Pinger-Websites vor. Sollte sich darüber hinaus ein Nutzer als Kind im Alter von unter 13 Jahren auf einer der Pinger-Websites identifizieren, wird Pinger keine persönlichen Daten eines solchen Nutzers sammeln, speichern oder verwenden. Sollte Pinger persönliche Daten erhalten und später feststellen, dass sie von einem Kind im Alter von unter 13 Jahren bereitgestellt wurden, wird Pinger diese persönlichen Daten unverzüglich auf sichere Weise löschen.

**Links zu Seiten von Drittparteien**

Wir können für Sie Links und/oder Verbindungen zu Websites oder Diensten von Drittparteien von unseren Websites oder unseren Produkten oder Dienstleistungen aus bereitstellen. Pinger ist nicht für die Datenschutzpraktiken oder den Inhalt dieser Websites von Drittparteien verantwortlich.

**Einsicht/Löschen Ihrer persönlichen Informationen**

Sollten Sie wünschen, dass wir Ihre persönlichen Daten aus unserer Datenbank löschen, oder wenn Sie auf die von Ihnen erfassten persönlichen Daten zugreifen möchten, können Sie uns über die nachfolgend angegebenen Kontaktinformationen benachrichtigen. Nach Beendigung der Pinger-Dienstleistungen werden Ihre persönlichen Daten gelöscht. Gewisse Produkte und Dienstleistungen von uns erfordern die Verwendung von App-Daten und derartige Daten werden von Pinger entsprechend der Beschreibung in dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie und der Nutzervereinbarung für die zutreffenden Produkte und Dienstleistungen aufbewahrt und verwendet.

**Änderungen der Datenschutzrichtlinie**

Pinger behält sich das Recht vor, diese Datenschutzrichtlinie nach eigenem Ermessen zu jedem Zeitpunkt zu ändern, zu aktualisieren oder zu modifizieren, indem solch eine Veränderung, Aktualisierung oder Modifizierung auf den Pinger-Websites mitgeteilt wird; dies erfolgt mit sofortiger Wirkung nach der Bekanntgabe, die Pinger auf jegliche Weise durchführen kann, insbesondere durch Mitteilungen auf den Pinger-Websites, Benachrichtigungen innerhalb von Pinger-Anwendungen oder per E-Mail. Ihre weitere Nutzung der Pinger-Websites und/oder jeglicher Pinger-Produkte und -Dienstleistungen im Anschluss an die Veröffentlichung solcher Änderungen bedeutet, dass Sie diese Änderungen akzeptieren. Die Verwendung der von uns erfassten Informationen unterliegt der Datenschutzrichtlinie, die zum Zeitpunkt der Nutzung in Kraft ist.

Kontaktieren Sie uns  

Sollten Sie Fragen oder Bedenken hinsichtlich dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie haben, wie z. B., welche persönlichen Daten über Sie gespeichert werden, senden Sie uns bitte eine E-Mail an [info@pinger.com](mailto:info@pinger.com). Sollten wir offizielle Beschwerden in Bezug auf den Datenschutz erhalten, besteht unsere Richtlinie darin, dass wir angemessene Bemühungen aufwenden, um das Anliegen mit der beschwerdeführenden Partei zu erörtern und die Datenschutzbeschwerde zu lösen. Für die Zwecke dieser Datenschutzrichtlinie bedeutet „Pinger“ entweder Pinger (UK) Ltd. oder Pinger International Ltd., je nachdem, mit welchem der Unternehmen Sie einen Nutzungsvertrag abgeschlossen haben.

Zuletzt aktualisiert am 1. März 2012  

Generalidades

Esta Política de protección de la información describe la forma en que Pinger trata la información, incluso los datos personales, que es recopilada y recibida en relación con su uso de productos, servicios y sitios web de Pinger.

La información que Pinger recopila y utiliza

Pinger recopila información cuando usted utiliza y accede a sus productos, servicios y sitios web. La información recopilada incluye información personal, información de aplicaciones, información de tráfico e información de participación (denominado colectivamente, la “Información del cliente”). La “información personal” es aquella que usted proporciona, que puede ser utilizada para identificarlo directamente, como su nombre completo, dirección, dirección de correo electrónico, información de facturación, número de teléfono de la casa y dirección del trabajo. No se recopila información personal cuando usted solamente accede a las áreas públicas de nuestros sitios web. La “información de aplicaciones” es aquella sobre la naturaleza de su uso de los sitios web, productos y servicios de Pinger, así como información demográfica no personal. La información de aplicaciones incluye: Direcciones de protocolo de Internet (IP), servidores de dominio, páginas referenciales/de salida, información del sistema operativo, tipo de navegador web, sello de fecha/hora e información sobre el flujo de visitas; y para los productos y servicios de Pinger, la información de aplicaciones también incluye identificadores de dispositivos, mensajes enviados y recibidos utilizando los servicios de Pinger, información sobre aquellos mensajes, tipo de dispositivo, información de ubicación, edad del usuario y demografía de sexo, tipo de navegador, información de la portadora e información y estadísticas sobre el uso de las aplicaciones del producto de Pinger. La “información de participación” es aquella que usted nos brinda para utilizarla con los productos o servicios de Pinger y la cual puede estar disponible para terceros por sus acciones al utilizar los productos o servicios de Pinger.

**Uso y procesamiento de la información, distribución y divulgación**

Pinger utiliza y procesa la Información del cliente que procesa para ofrecer, mejorar y modificar los productos y servicios de Pinger, para autenticar usuarios, brindar atención y servicio al cliente, comunicarse con usuarios a través de los productos y servicios de Pinger, publicar y ofrecer publicidad a través de nuestros productos y servicios, para notificaciones sobre los productos de Pinger, detección de fraude y cumplimiento de los acuerdos de los usuarios, así como para enviar, compartir y almacenar su información de participación como usted lo indique a través del uso de los productos y servicios de Pinger. Pinger procesa la Información del cliente, incluida la información personal, que figura en nuestros servidores en Estados Unidos de Norteamérica y en los países adicionales donde podamos añadir servidores.  En algunos casos, podemos procesar Información del cliente a nombre de, a través de, o de acuerdo a las indicaciones de un tercero, como nuestros socios publicistas, pero solo cuando usted nos ha proporcionado su consentimiento expreso, informado e irrevocable para hacerlo. Pinger no alquila, vende o distribuye la Información del cliente, a menos que contemos con su consentimiento expreso informado y conforme a las siguientes circunstancias: (i) Pinger puede involucrar a un tercero de confianza para que lleve a cabo funciones limitadas en nuestra representación, como llenar suscripciones para boletines informativos, enviar y recibir correspondencia solicitada, ya sea por correo postal, electrónico, mensajes de texto telefónico e informático y comunicaciones de voz, así como brindar servicio al cliente, analizar y procesar información (como información de facturación) y suministrar información publicitaria. Nosotros exigimos que estas partes acepten utilizar dicha información en forma confidencial y en cumplimiento con esta Política de protección de la información. Estos terceros pueden tener acceso a la información personal necesaria para desempeñar sus funciones, pero no les permitimos utilizarla con otro propósito sin su consentimiento, excepto según sea exigido por la ley vigente. (ii) Pinger puede compartir información de aplicaciones e información no personal a terceros, la cual no lo identifique en forma individual. (iii) Pinger puede compartir Información del cliente para responder ante requerimientos legales, cuando le sea legalmente exigido hacerlo y a solicitud de las autoridades gubernamentales. (iv) Pinger puede compartir Información del cliente para verificar o hacer cumplir los acuerdos de los usuarios y las leyes vigentes, para protegerse contra el fraude, detectar y evitar problemas de seguridad o técnicos, protegerse contra el uso incorrecto o no autorizado de los productos, servicios, sistemas informáticos o sitios web de Pinger, o para protegerse contra daños a la propiedad, a los derechos o a la seguridad de Pinger, sus suscriptores o el público. (v) Pinger puede compartir Información del cliente con una entidad sucesora o en relación con una fusión corporativa, consolidación, venta de activos u otro tipo de reorganización corporativa, siempre que el uso de la Información del cliente se haga en cumplimiento de esta Política de protección de la información. (vi) Pinger puede compartir Información del cliente con un tercero si usted ha consentido recibir información de, o compartirla con, ese tercero a través de los productos o servicios de Pinger. Tales terceros manejarán, almacenarán, conservarán y accederán a dicha Información del cliente de acuerdo a los términos y condiciones de sus acuerdos con usted, si los hubiera, así como de acuerdo a sus propias políticas de protección de la información. Es su responsabilidad revisar con atención dichos acuerdos y políticas de protección de la información. Usted reconoce que Pinger no tendrá responsabilidad ante usted por compartir dicha información a tales terceros y Pinger renuncia a toda responsabilidad relacionada con la misma. (vii) A fin de proporcionarle software y servicios, Pinger puede compartir Información del cliente con su casa matriz y/o subsidiarias dentro y fuera de la Unión Europea y esas partes pueden procesar y almacenar la Información del cliente en cualquier país del mundo, sujeto a esta Política de protección de la información.

**Huellas informáticas (cookies)**

Cuando usted visita Pinger, nosotros podemos enviar huellas informáticas a su computadora, las que identifican en forma única su navegador o etiquetas de píxeles (algunas veces denominadas balizas web) para registrar las páginas visitadas. Nosotros utilizamos huellas informáticas y etiquetas para mejorar la calidad de nuestro servicio, almacenando las preferencias de los usuarios y dándole seguimiento a la información de uso. La mayoría de los navegadores le permiten deshabilitar las huellas informáticas o configurar su navegador para advertirle cuando se están enviando huellas informáticas a su computadora. También podemos incluir etiquetas en material promocional a fin de determinar si los mensajes se han abierto y se ha actuado sobre los mismos. Por el presente, usted otorga su consentimiento en forma expresa para que Pinger tenga el derecho de colocar estas huellas informáticas y etiquetas para los servicios antes mencionados en su computadora o dispositivo. Si usted desactiva las huevas informáticas, es posible que no pueda utilizar ciertos productos y servicios de Pinger.

Información de tráfico  

La información de tráfico de telecomunicaciones (“Información de tráfico”) se recopila en relación con su uso de los servicios de Pinger y se almacena después de finalizada la comunicación, para fines de facturación y hasta por los periodos máximos autorizados por la ley vigente, después de lo cual será eliminada, a menos que (i) usted haya planteado objeciones contra la facturación; o (ii) si hay sospecha razonable de fraude o de otra actividad criminal. Para efectos del cumplimiento de la ley, la Información de tráfico también se almacena en cumplimiento con la ley vigente para la conservación de información. La Información de tráfico almacenada de acuerdo a esta segunda oración no puede ser utilizada por usted para fines de una disputa de facturación.

**Seguridad e integridad de la información**

Nosotros contamos con salvaguardas físicos, electrónicos y de procedimiento para proteger la pérdida, el uso incorrecto y la alteración de la Información del cliente que se encuentre bajo nuestro control. La Información del cliente que recopilamos se almacena en forma segura, accesible únicamente por el personal, los contratistas y agentes autorizados de Pinger, vinculados por obligaciones de confidencialidad y solo se divulga conforme a las disposiciones de esta Política de protección de la información. Nuestro procesamiento de la información personal tiene el único propósito por la que fue recopilada en primer lugar o de otro modo, de conformidad con esta Política de protección de la información y las leyes de protección de la información nacional y de la Unión Europea vigentes. Periódicamente, Pinger realiza una revisión de sus prácticas de privacidad para asegurar que la información que recopilamos sea necesaria para brindar o mejorar los servicios que ofrecemos.

Información personal de los niños  

Los sitios web de Pinger cumplen con la Ley de Protección de Privacidad Infantil en Línea (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, COPPA). Pinger no recopila, a sabiendas, información personal de niños menores de 13 años de edad a través de las páginas web de Pinger. Además, en el caso que un usuario se identifique como un niño menor de 13 años de edad dentro de los sitios web de Pinger, este no recopilará, almacenará o utilizará ninguna información personal de tal usuario. Asimismo, en el caso que Pinger reciba información personal que descubra haber sido proporcionada por un niño menor de 13 años de edad, Pinger eliminará inmediatamente dicha información personal en forma segura.

**Enlaces a sitios de terceros**

Por su comodidad, podemos proporcionar enlaces y/o conexiones a sitios web o servicios de terceros dentro de nuestros sitios web o de nuestros productos o servicios. Pinger no es responsable de las prácticas de privacidad o contenido de estos sitios de terceros.

**Acceso/eliminación de su información personal**

Si desea que eliminemos su información personal de nuestra base de datos o quisiera acceder a la misma que se haya recopilado sobre usted, puede comunicarse con nosotros utilizando la información de contacto proporcionada más adelante. Su información personal será eliminada, tras la finalización de los servicios de Pinger. Algunos de nuestros productos y servicios requieren el uso de información de aplicaciones y que la misma sea conservada por Pinger y utilizada según lo descrito en esta Política de protección de la información, así como en los acuerdos de los usuarios finales para los productos y servicios correspondientes.

**Modificaciones de la Política de protección de la información**

Pinger se reserva el derecho, a su entera discreción, de cambiar, actualizar o modificar esta Política de protección de la información en cualquier momento, publicando dicho cambio, actualización o modificación en los sitios web de Pinger, la cual será efectiva en forma inmediata mediante aviso, el cual Pinger puede proporcionar mediante cualquier medio, lo que incluye, entre otros, publicación en sus sitios web, notificaciones dentro de sus aplicaciones o correo electrónico. Su uso continuo de los sitios web de Pinger y/o cualquiera de sus productos y servicios después de la publicación de los cambios significará que usted acepta esos cambios. El uso de la información que recopilamos está sujeto a la Política de protección de la información vigente al momento de su uso.

Contáctenos  

Si tiene alguna pregunta o inquietud con respecto a esta Política de protección de la información, tal como qué información personal se almacena sobre usted, envíenos un correo electrónico a [info@pinger.com](mailto:info@pinger.com). Si recibimos reclamos formales relacionados a la privacidad, es nuestra política llevar a cabo esfuerzos razonables para comunicarnos con la parte que presenta el reclamo, para tratar sus inquietudes y resolver los reclamos de privacidad. Para los efectos de esta Política de protección de la información, “Pinger” se referirá a Pinger (UK) Ltd. o Pinger International Ltd., según el acuerdo de usuarios de la entidad que usted haya aceptado.

Actualizado por última vez el 1 de marzo de 2012.  

Présentation

La présente Politique de protection des données décrit comment Pinger traite les données, y compris personnelles, qu’elle recueille et reçoit sur votre utilisation des produits, services et sites Web Pinger.

Informations recueillies et utilisées par Pinger

Pinger recueille ces données lorsque vous utilisez les produits, services et sites Web Pinger et accédez à ceux-ci. Les informations ainsi recueillies comprennent les Données personnelles, les Données d’application, les Données sur le trafic et les Données pour partage (collectivement les « Informations client »). Les « Données personnelles » sont les informations fournies par vous et pouvant être utilisées pour vous identifier directement, comme vos nom et prénom, adresse électronique, détails de facturation, numéro de téléphone personnel et adresses personnelle et professionnelle. Aucune Donnée personnelle n’est recueillie lorsque vous accédez simplement aux zones publiques de nos sites Web. Les « Données d’application » sont des informations sur la nature de votre usage des sites Web, produits et services Pinger et des informations démographiques non personnelles. Les Données d’application incluent : les adresses IP, les serveurs de domaines, les pages de consultation/sortie, les informations sur les systèmes d’exploitation, le type de navigateur Web, l’horodatage, et les données de parcours de navigation ; et, concernant les produits et services Pinger, les Données d’application comprennent également les identificateurs des dispositifs, les messages envoyés et reçus à l’aide des services Pinger, les informations sur ces messages, le type de dispositif, les informations de localisation, l’âge et le genre de l’utilisateur, le type de navigateur, les informations sur l’opérateur, et les informations et statistiques sur l’utilisation des fonctions des produits Pinger. Les « Données pour partage » sont les données que vous fournissez pour utilisation avec les produits ou services Pinger et qui peuvent être communiquées à des tiers par vos actions lors de l’utilisation des produits ou services Pinger.

**Utilisation et traitement des informations ; partage et divulgation**

Pinger utilise et traite les Informations client pour fournir, améliorer et modifier les produits et services Pinger, pour authentifier les utilisateurs, pour fournir un service et un soutien à la clientèle, pour communiquer avec les utilisateurs au moyen des produits et services Pinger, pour publier et produire des annonces au moyen de nos produits et services, pour les notifications des produits Pinger, pour la détection des fraudes et la conformité aux contrats d’utilisation, et pour envoyer, partager et stocker vos Données pour partage selon vos directives lors de l’utilisation des produits et services Pinger. Pinger traite les Informations client, Données personnelles comprises, sur nos serveurs des États-Unis d’Amérique et des autres pays où nous pouvons installer des serveurs. Dans certains cas, il se peut que nous traitions les Informations client au nom, par l’intermédiaire ou selon les instructions de tiers tels que nos partenaires publicitaires, mais seulement si vous avez donné votre accord exprès, informé et révocable à cet effet.

Pinger ne loue, ne vend ni ne partage les Informations client sauf si nous avons votre accord exprès et informé, et dans les circonstances suivantes.

(i) Pinger peut engager un tiers de confiance pour accomplir en notre nom des fonctions limitées, comme gérer les abonnements à des bulletins d’informations, envoyer et recevoir les courriers postaux, courriels, SMS, MMS et communications vocales requis, analyser et traiter des données (tels que les détails de facturation), fournir des services publicitaires et des services à la clientèle. Nous exigeons de ces tiers qu’ils s’engagent à utiliser ces informations de façon confidentielle et conformément à la présente Politique de protection des données. Il se peut que ces tiers accèdent aux Données personnelles nécessaires pour accomplir leurs fonctions, mais nous ne les autorisons pas à les utiliser à d’autres fins sans votre consentement, sauf si la législation en vigueur l’exige.

(ii) Il se peut que Pinger partage avec des tiers des Données d’application et informations non personnelles ne vous identifiant pas personnellement.

(iii) Il se peut que Pinger partage les Informations client pour répondre aux exigences légales, si elle est légalement tenue de le faire, et à la demande des autorités gouvernementales.

(iv) Il se peut que Pinger partage les Informations client pour vérifier ou appliquer la conformité aux contrats d’utilisation et à la législation en vigueur, pour la protection anti-fraude, pour détecter et prévenir tous problèmes techniques ou de sécurité, pour la protection contre le mauvais usage ou l’utilisation non autorisée des produits, services, systèmes informatiques ou sites Web Pinger, ou pour la protection contre toute violation des droits, de la propriété ou de la sécurité de Pinger, de ses abonnés ou du public.

(v) Il se peut que Pinger partage les Informations client avec une entité remplaçante ou suite à une fusion, un regroupement d’entreprises, une vente des actifs ou autre réorganisation d’entreprise sous réserve que l’utilisation des Informations client soit conforme à la présente Politique de protection des données.

(vi) Il se peut que Pinger partage les Informations client avec un tiers si vous avez consenti à recevoir des informations de ce tiers ou à partager des informations avec ce tiers au moyen des produits ou services Pinger. Ces tiers traiteront, stockeront, conserveront et accéderont à ces Informations client selon les modalités et conditions de leurs accords avec vous, s’il y a lieu, et selon leurs propres politiques de protection des données. Il vous incombe d’examiner avec soin ces accords et politiques de protection des données. Vous reconnaissez que Pinger n’a aucune obligation à votre égard pour le partage de ces informations avec des tiers, et Pinger dénie toute obligation à cet effet.

(vii) Afin de vous fournir ces logiciels et ces services, il se peut que Pinger partage les Informations client avec ses sociétés mères et/ou filiales dans ou hors de l’Union Européenne, et ces parties peuvent traiter et stocker les Informations client dans tout pays du monde sous réserve de la présente Politique de protection des données.

**Cookies**

Lorsque vous consultez Pinger, nous pouvons envoyer des cookies à votre ordinateur qui identifient exclusivement votre navigateur, ou utiliser des balises de pixels (désignées parfois par balises Web) pour enregistrer les pages consultées. Nous utilisons ces cookies et ces balises pour améliorer la qualité de nos services en stockant les préférences de l’utilisateur et en suivant les informations d’usage. La plupart des navigateurs vous permettent de désactiver ces cookies ou de configurer votre navigateur pour vous alerter quand des cookies sont envoyés à votre ordinateur. Il se peut que nous incluions également des balises dans des documents publicitaires afin de déterminer si les messages ont été ouverts et utilisés. Vous reconnaissez expressément par la présente que Pinger est en droit de placer ces cookies et balises pour les services susmentionnés sur votre ordinateur ou autre dispositif. Si vous désactivez ces cookies, il se peut que vous ne puissiez pas utiliser certains produits et services Pinger.

Données sur le trafic  

Les données sur le trafic des télécommunications (« Données sur le trafic ») sont recueillies au sujet de votre utilisation des services Pinger et sont stockées à la fin de la communication à des fins de facturation dans la limite des périodes autorisées par la législation en vigueur, et seront supprimées par la suite, à moins (i) que vous n’ayez objecté à la facturation, ou (ii) ou qu’il y ait un doute raisonnable de fraude ou d’autre activité criminelle. À des fins légales, les Données sur le trafic sont également stockées conformément à la législation en vigueur sur la conservation des données. Les Données sur le trafic stockées en vertu de ce second point ne pourront être utilisées par vous pour objecter à la facturation.

**Sécurité et intégrité des données**

Nous avons mis en place des protections physiques, électroniques et procédurales pour prémunir les Informations client sous notre contrôle de pertes, mauvais usages et altérations éventuels. Les Informations client que nous recueillons sont stockées de façon sécurisée et ne sont accessibles que par le personnel, les sous-traitants et les agents autorisés de Pinger liés par des obligations de confidentialité, et elles ne sont communiquées que conformément aux dispositions de la présente Politique de protection des données. Les Données personnelles ne sont traitées par nous qu’aux fins pour lesquelles elles ont été recueillies ou sinon en conformité avec la présente Politique de protection des données et les lois nationales et de l’Union Européenne en vigueur sur la protection des données. Périodiquement, Pinger revoit ses pratiques de protection de la vie privée afin de s’assurer que les informations recueillies sont bien nécessaires à la prestation ou à l’amélioration des services que nous fournissons.

Informations personnelles concernant les enfants  

Les sites Web de Pinger sont conformes à la loi des États-Unis sur la protection de la vie privée des enfants (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, COPPA). Pinger veille, dans la limite de ses connaissances, à ne pas recueillir les Données personnelles d’enfants âgés de moins de 13 ans au moyen des sites Web Pinger. De plus, si un utilisateur s’identifie comme un enfant de moins de 13 ans sur les sites Web Pinger, Pinger ne recueillera, ne stockera ni n’utilisera aucune Donnée personnelle le concernant. Par ailleurs, si Pinger reçoit des Données personnelles dont elle découvre qu’elles ont été fournies par un enfant de moins de 13 ans, Pinger supprimera promptement ces Données personnelles de façon sécurisée.

**Liens avec des sites de tiers**

Pour votre commodité, il se peut que nous fournissions des liens et/ou connexions avec des sites Web ou services de tiers depuis nos propres sites Web, produits ou services. Pinger n’est pas responsable des pratiques de protection de la vie privée ou du contenu de ces sites tiers.

**Accès/suppression de vos informations personnelles**

Si vous souhaitez que nous supprimions vos Données personnelles de notre base de données, ou accéder aux Données personnelles que nous avons recueillies, vous pouvez nous contacter en utilisant les coordonnées indiquées ci-dessous. Dès cessation des services Pinger, vos Données personnelles seront supprimées. Certains de nos produits et services exigent l’utilisation des Données d’application, et ces données sont conservées par Pinger et utilisées dans le cadre de la présente Politique de protection des données et des accords avec les utilisateurs finaux concernant les produits et services utilisés.

**Modifications de la politique de protection des données**

Pinger se réserve le droit, à sa discrétion, de changer, mettre à jour ou modifier la présente Politique de protection des données, à tout moment, en affichant lesdits changements, mises à jour ou modifications sur les sites Web Pinger. Ils prendront effet immédiatement après un préavis donné par Pinger selon le moyen de son choix à savoir, sans limitation, l’affichage sur les sites Web Pinger, des notifications dans les applications Pinger, ou le courrier électronique. Votre utilisation subséquente des sites Web Pinger et/ou de tous produits et services Pinger suite à l’affichage de ces changements signifiera que vous acceptez ces changements. L’utilisation des informations recueillies par nous est soumise à la Politique de protection des données en vigueur lors de leur utilisation.

Nous contacter  

Pour toutes questions ou préoccupations concernant la présente Politique de protection des données, par exemple quelles Données personnelles sont stockées vous concernant, veuillez nous contacter par courriel à [info@pinger.com](mailto:info@pinger.com). Dans le cas d’une plainte formelle pour non-protection de la vie privée, notre politique exige que nous déployons des efforts raisonnables pour communiquer avec la partie plaignante afin de connaître et remédier à une telle plainte. Aux fins de la présente Politique de protection des données, « Pinger » signifie Pinger (UK) Ltd. ou Pinger International Ltd., selon l’entité auprès de laquelle vous avez souscrit votre contrat d’utilisation.

Dernière mise à jour le 1er mars 2012  

Panoramica

La presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati spiega in che modo Pinger gestisce i dati, inclusi quelli personali, che raccoglie e riceve in seguito all’utilizzo da parte dell’utente di prodotti, servizi e siti Web Pinger.

Le informazioni raccolte e utilizzate da Pinger

Pinger raccoglie dati quando l’utente accede ai prodotti, servizi e siti Web di Pinger. Le informazioni raccolte includono Dati personali, Dati di applicazione, traffico e condivisione (collettivamente, le “Informazioni del cliente”). I “Dati personali” sono informazioni fornite dall’utente che possono essere utilizzate per identificare direttamente la sua persona, come nome e cognome, indirizzo email, informazioni di fatturazione, recapito telefonico e indirizzo di abitazione e ufficio. I Dati personali non vengono raccolti quando si accede semplicemente alle aree pubbliche dei nostri siti Web. I “Dati di applicazione” sono informazioni relative alla natura dell’uso da parte dell’utente di siti Web, prodotti e servizi di Pinger; sono inoltre informazioni demografiche di uso generico. I Dati di applicazione includono: indirizzi IP, server di dominio, pagine di riferimento/uscita, informazioni sul sistema operativo, tipo di browser Web, indicatore di data/ora, e dati clickstream; per quanto riguarda i prodotti e i servizi di Pinger, i Dati di applicazione includono anche identificatori di dispositivo, messaggi inviati e ricevuti usando i servizi Pinger, informazioni relative a questi messaggi, tipo di dispositivo, informazioni sulla posizione, dati demografici relativi all’età e al sesso dell’utente, tipo di browser, informazioni sul vettore, e informazioni e statistiche sull’uso delle funzionalità dei prodotti Pinger. I “Dati di condivisione” sono dati forniti dall’utente per utilizzare i prodotti e i servizi Pinger, e che potrebbero essere rese disponibili a terzi in seguito ad azioni dell’utente stesso durante l’uso dei prodotti o servizi di Pinger.

**Utilizzo ed elaborazione delle informazioni; Condivisione e divulgazione**

Pinger utilizza ed elabora le Informazioni del cliente per fornire, migliorare e modificare i prodotti e servizi di Pinger, per autenticare gli utenti, fornire assistenza e servizio alla clientela, per comunicare con gli utenti mediante i suoi prodotti e servizi, per pubblicare e fornire materiale pubblicitario mediante i suoi prodotti e servizi, per le notifiche sui suoi prodotti, per il rilevamento di frodi e la conformità ai contratti con l’utente, e per inviare, condividere e memorizzare i Dati di condivisione dell’utente mediante l’uso di prodotti e servizi Pinger. Pinger elabora le Informazioni del cliente, inclusi i dati personali, sui nostri server negli Stati Uniti d’America e in eventuali altri Paesi in cui potremmo aggiungere i nostri server. In alcuni casi, potremmo elaborare le Informazioni del cliente in nome e per conto di, o conformemente alle indicazioni di una terza parte, come ad esempio i nostri partner pubblicitari, ma solo se l’utente abbia fornito espressamente il proprio consenso informato e revocabile per agire in tal senso.

Pinger non cede, vende, né condivide le Informazioni del cliente a meno che non abbia ricevuto l’esplicito consenso informato dell’utente, e nelle seguenti circostanze:

(i) Pinger può assumere una terza parte di fiducia per svolgere funzioni limitate a suo nome, tra cui il completamento delle iscrizioni alla newsletter, l’invio e la ricezione di posta ordinaria, posta elettronica, SMS, MMS, e comunicazioni vocali, l’analisi e l’elaborazione di dati (ad esempio le informazioni di fatturazione), l’ad serving, e la fornitura del servizio clienti. Pretendiamo che tali terze parti accettino di usare dette informazioni in modo riservato e conforme alla Politica sulla protezione dei dati in oggetto. Le terze parti di cui sopra possono accedere ai Dati personali necessari per svolgere le loro funzioni; tuttavia non permettiamo loro di utilizzarli per altri scopi senza il consenso dell’utente, salvo quanto previsto dalle leggi in vigore.

(ii) Pinger può condividere con le terze parti i Dati di applicazione e le informazioni non personali che non identificano personalmente l’utente.

(iii) Pinger può condividere le Informazioni del cliente per soddisfare i requisiti legali, se previsto dalla legge, e su richiesta di agenzie governative.

(iv) Pinger può condividere le Informazioni del cliente per verificare o imporre la conformità ai contratti con l’utente e alle leggi in vigore, per applicare la protezione contro le frodi, rilevare ed evitare problemi tecnici o sulla sicurezza, per impedire l’uso improprio o non autorizzato dei prodotti, servizi, sistemi informatici o siti Web di Pinger, o per impedire la violazione dei diritti, delle proprietà o della sicurezza di Pinger, dei suoi utenti o del pubblico.

(v) Pinger può condividere le Informazioni del cliente con un successore o in relazione ad una fusione aziendale, consolidamento, vendita di beni o altri tipi di riorganizzazione aziendale, a condizione che l’uso delle Informazioni del cliente sia conforme alla presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati.

(vi) Pinger può condividere le Informazioni del cliente con una terza parte nel caso in cui l’utente abbia fornito il proprio consenso per ricevere informazioni da, o condividerle con tale terza parte mediante i prodotti o servizi Pinger. Tali terze parti potranno gestire, archiviare, conservare e accedere alle Informazioni del cliente conformemente ai termini e condizioni dei loro accordi con l’utente, ove presenti, oltre che alle relative politiche sulla protezione dei dati. È responsabilità dell’utente esaminare attentamente tali accordi e le politiche sulla protezione dei dati. L’utente conviene che Pinger non avrà responsabilità nei suoi confronti relativamente alla condivisione di tali informazioni con terze parti, e che Pinger declina qualsiasi responsabilità a riguardo.

(vii) Al fine di fornire all’utente software e servizi, Pinger può condividere le Informazioni del cliente con le sue società controllanti e/o controllate all’interno e all’esterno dell’Unione Europea; queste parti inoltre possono elaborare e memorizzare le Informazioni dell’utente in ogni Paese del mondo subordinatamente alla presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati.

**Cookies**

Quando un utente visita Pinger, il nostro sistema potrebbe inviare al suo computer dei cookie che identificano in modo univoco il browser, oppure potrebbe utilizzare dei pixel tag (a volte chiamati anche Web beacon) per registrare le pagine visitate. Cookie e tag vengono utilizzati per migliorare la qualità del nostro servizio, mediante memorizzazione delle preferenze degli utenti e controllo delle informazioni relative all’utilizzo. Molti browser consentono all’utente di disabilitare i cookie, o di impostare un avviso ogni qualvolta i cookie stanno per essere inviati sul computer. È possibile anche che il nostro sistema inserisca i tag nel materiale promozionale, al fine di stabilire se i messaggi sono stati aperti e utilizzati. Con la presente, l’utente fornisce il suo consenso esplicito affinché Pinger possa inserire cookie e tag nel suo computer o dispositivo per i servizi summenzionati. Disabilitando i cookie, l’utente non potrà utilizzare alcuni prodotti e servizi di Pinger.

Dati di traffico  

I dati relativi alle telecomunicazioni (“Dati di traffico”) vengono raccolti in relazione all’uso da parte dell’utente dei servizi Pinger, e vengono memorizzati alla fine della comunicazione per motivi di fatturazione, fino al periodo massimo consentito dalle leggi in vigore; al termine di questo periodo, tali dati verranno cancellati a meno che (i) l’utente non sollevi obiezioni relativamente alla fattura, o (ii) nel caso in cui ci sia un sospetto ragionevole di frode o di altra attività criminale. Ai fini dell’applicazione di legge, i Dati di traffico vengono inoltre memorizzati conformemente alla legislazione vigente in materia di conservazione dei dati. I Dati di traffico archiviati ai sensi di questo secondo paragrafo non potranno essere utilizzati dall’utente per la risoluzione di una controversia relativa alla fatturazione.

**Sicurezza e integrità dei dati**

Disponiamo di sistemi di tutela fisica, elettronica e procedurale per impedire la perdita, l’uso improprio e l’alterazione delle Informazioni del cliente in nostro possesso. Le Informazioni del cliente da noi raccolte vengono memorizzate in modo sicuro e sono accessibili solo da personale, appaltatori e agenti autorizzati da Pinger, vincolati da obblighi di riservatezza; inoltre tali informazioni vengono divulgate solo ai sensi delle disposizioni contenute nella presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati. I Dati personali vengono da noi elaborati al solo scopo per cui sono stati raccolti, o diversamente, in conformità alla presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati e alle leggi in vigore a livello nazionale ed europeo in materia di protezione dei dati. Periodicamente, Pinger effettua una revisione delle sue informative sulla privacy, per garantire che le informazioni da noi raccolte siano necessarie per fornire o migliorare i nostri servizi.

Informazioni personali dei minori  

I siti Web di Pinger sono conformi al Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), il regolamento che tutela la privacy dei minori sul Web. Attraverso i siti Web di Pinger, Pinger non raccoglie consapevolmente Dati personali da bambini di età inferiore ai 13 anni. Inoltre, nel caso in cui all’interno dei siti Web di Pinger un utente si identifichi come un bambino di età inferiore ai 13 anni, Pinger non raccoglierà, memorizzerà o utilizzerà i Dati personali di tale utente. In aggiunta, nel caso in cui Pinger riceva Dati personali che Pinger scoprirà essere stati forniti da un bambino di età inferiore ai 13 anni, Pinger provvederà ad eliminare immediatamente tali Dati personali in maniera sicura.

**Collegamenti a siti di terzi**

Per comodità dell’utente, potremmo fornire link e/o collegamenti a siti Web o servizi di terzi dai nostri siti Web, prodotti o servizi. Pinger non è responsabile delle informative sulla privacy o dei contenuti di questi siti Web di terze parti.

**Accesso/rimozione delle Informazioni personali**

Se l’utente desidera che i suoi Dati personali vengano eliminati dal nostro database, o se desidera accedere ai propri Dati personali raccolti, può contattarci usando le informazioni fornite di seguito. Alla cessazione dei servizi Pinger, i Dati personali dell’utente verranno cancellati. Alcuni dei nostri prodotti e servizi richiedono l’uso di Dati di applicazione, che vengono conservati da Pinger e utilizzati secondo quanto descritto nella presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati e nei contratti con l’utente finale relativamente ai prodotti e servizi applicabili.

**Modifiche alla Politica sulla protezione dei dati**

Pinger si riserva il diritto, a sua discrezione, di cambiare, aggiornare o modificare in qualsiasi momento la presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati, pubblicando sui siti Web di Pinger tali cambiamenti, aggiornamenti o modifiche, che saranno effettivi subito dopo l’avviso che Pinger potrà fornire in qualsiasi modo, incluse, in maniera del tutto esemplificativa, la pubblicazione sui siti Web Pinger, notifiche all’interno di applicazioni Pinger, o posta elettronica. L’utilizzo continuativo dei siti Web di Pinger e/o di qualsivoglia prodotto e servizio di Pinger successivo alla pubblicazione delle modifiche, starà a significare l’accettazione da parte dell’utente di tali modifiche. L’impiego delle informazioni da noi raccolte è soggetto alla Politica sulla protezione dei dati, in vigore dal momento del suo utilizzo.

Contatti  

In caso di dubbi o domande relativamente alla nostra Politica sulla protezione dei dati (ad esempio, quali tipi di Dati personali vengono memorizzati), inviare un’email all’indirizzo info@pinger.com. In caso di reclami formali relativi alla privacy, la nostra politica prevede il ricorso a sforzi ragionevoli per dialogare con la parte querelante e cercare di risolvere il problema. Ai sensi della presente Politica sulla protezione dei dati, “Pinger” sta ad indicare sia Pinger (UK) Ltd., che Pinger International Ltd,. a seconda di quale dei due contratti con l’utente sia stato accettato.

Ultimo aggiornamento: 1 marzo 2012

Visão geral

Esta Política de Protecção de Dados descreve a forma como a Pinger trata os dados, incluindo os dados pessoais, que recolhe e recebe relacionados com a sua utilização de produtos, serviços e sítios web da Pinger.

Informação recolhida e utilizada pela Pinger

A Pinger recolhe dados aquando da sua utilização e do seu acesso aos produtos, serviços e sítios web da Pinger. As informações recolhidas incluem Dados pessoais, Dados de aplicações, Dados de tráfego e Dados de partilha (colectivamente, “Informações do Cliente”). “Dados pessoais” são as informações fornecidas por si e que podem ser utilizadas para o identificar directamente, como o seu nome completo, morada, endereço de e-mail, dados de facturação, número de telefone de casa e moradas de casa e do local de trabalho. Não são recolhidos quaisquer Dados pessoais quando acede apenas às áreas públicas dos nossos sítios web. “Dados de aplicações” são informações acerca da natureza da sua utilização dos sítios web e produtos e serviços da Pinger e informações demográficas não pessoais. Dados de aplicações incluem: endereços IP, servidores de domínios, páginas de entrada/saída, informações do sistema operativo, tipo de browser web, marca de data/hora e dados de sequência de cliques; e para os produtos e serviços da Pinger os Dados de aplicações também incluem identificadores de aparelhos, mensagens enviadas e recebidas através dos serviços da Pinger, informações acerca dessas mensagens, tipo de aparelho, informações de localização, idade e sexo do utilizador, tipo de browser, informações de operador e informações e estatísticas acerca da utilização das características dos produtos da Pinger. “Dados de partilha” são os dados que fornece para utilizar com os produtos ou serviços da Pinger e que podem ser disponibilizados a terceiros através das suas acções aquando da sua utilização de produtos ou serviços da Pinger.

**Utilização e processamento de informações; Partilha e publicação**

A Pinger utiliza e processa as Informações do Cliente para fornecer, melhorar e modificar os produtos e serviços da Pinger, para autenticar utilizadores, para prestar apoio e serviço a clientes, para comunicar com utilizadores através dos produtos e serviços da Pinger, para publicar e fornecer publicidade através dos nossos produtos e serviços, para notificações dos produtos da Pinger, para detecção de fraude e conformidade com os contratos de utilização e para enviar, partilhar e armazenar os seus Dados de partilha de acordo com as suas instruções através da utilização dos produtos e serviços da Pinger. A Pinger processa as Informações do Cliente, incluindo Dados pessoais, nos nossos servidores nos Estados Unidos da América e em outros países onde podemos adicionar servidores. Em alguns casos, podemos processar as Informações do Cliente por parte de, através de ou de acordo com as indicações de terceiros, tais como os nossos parceiros de publicidade, mas apenas se nos tiver fornecido o seu consentimento expresso, informado e revogável a permitir que o façamos.

A Pinger não concede, vende nem partilha quaisquer Informações do Cliente, a menos que tenhamos o seu consentimento expresso e informado e nas seguintes circunstâncias:

(i) A Pinger pode envolver um terceiro da sua confiança para exercer funções limitadas em nosso nome, tais como o preenchimento de subscrições de newsletters, envio e recepção de correio terrestre solicitado, e-mails, SMS, MMS e comunicações de voz, análise e processamento de dados (tais como dados de facturação) e serviços de publicidade e para prestar serviços de atendimento ao cliente. Exigimos que estas partes concordem em utilizar essas informações de forma confidencial e em conformidade com esta Política de Protecção de Dados. Estes terceiros podem ter acesso aos Dados pessoais necessários para executarem as suas funções, mas não lhes permitimos que os utilizem para outros fins sem o seu consentimento, excepto se exigido ao abrigo da legislação aplicável.

(ii) A Pinger pode partilhar com terceiros os Dados de aplicações e informações não pessoais, que não o identifiquem individualmente.

(iii) A Pinger pode partilhar as Informações do Cliente para responder a obrigações legais, quando legalmente obrigada a fazê-lo, e a pedido das autoridades governamentais.

(iv) A Pinger pode partilhar as Informações do Cliente para verificar ou fazer cumprir a conformidade com os contratos de utilizador e a legislação aplicável, para proteger contra a fraude, para detectar e prevenir problemas de segurança ou problemas técnicos, para proteger contra a má utilização ou utilização não autorizada de produtos, serviços, sistemas de computação ou sítios web da Pinger ou para proteger contra ameaças aos direitos, propriedade ou segurança da Pinger, dos seus subscritores ou do público.

(v) A Pinger pode partilhar as Informações do Cliente com uma entidade sucessora ou relacionada com uma fusão empresarial, consolidação, venda de bens ou outra reorganização empresarial, desde que a utilização das Informações do Cliente esteja em conformidade com esta Política de Protecção de Dados.

(vi) A Pinger pode partilhar as Informações do Cliente com terceiros, caso o utilizador tenha permitido receber informações de, ou partilhar com, esse terceiro através dos produtos ou serviços da Pinger. Esses terceiros irão lidar, armazenar, reter ou aceder a essas Informações do Cliente de acordo com os termos e condições dos seus contratos consigo, se existentes, assim como com as suas próprias políticas de protecção de dados. É da sua responsabilidade analisar cuidadosamente esses contratos e políticas de protecção de dados. O utilizador reconhece que a Pinger não deve ter qualquer responsabilidade para consigo pela partilha dessas informações com esses terceiros e a Pinger declina toda e qualquer responsabilidade relacionada com a mesma.

(vii) De forma a fornecer-lhe software e serviços, a Pinger pode partilhar as Informações do Cliente com a sua empresa matriz e/ou empresas subsidiárias dentro e fora da União Europeia e estas partes podem processar e armazenar as Informações do Cliente em qualquer país do mundo, sujeitas a esta Política de Protecção de Dados.

**Cookies**

Quando visitar a Pinger, podemos enviar cookies para o seu computador que identificam de forma única o seu browser ou utilizam pixel tags (por vezes designados por web beacons) para registar as páginas visitadas. Utilizamos cookies e tags para melhorar a qualidade do nosso serviço ao armazenar as preferências do utilizador e rastrear informações de utilização. A maioria dos browsers permite desactivar os cookies ou definir o seu browser para que o alerte quando os cookies estiverem a ser enviados para o seu computador. Podemos também incluir tags em materiais promocionais de forma a determinar se as mensagens foram abertas e utilizadas. Pela presente, o utilizador autoriza expressamente a Pinger a colocar estes cookies e tags, para os serviços acima mencionados, no seu computador ou dispositivo. Se desactivar os cookies, poderá não conseguir utilizar certos produtos e serviços da Pinger.

Dados de tráfego  

Os dados de tráfego de telecomunicações (“Dados de tráfego”) são recolhidos relativamente à sua utilização dos serviços da Pinger e são armazenados após o final da comunicação para fins de facturação, até aos períodos máximos autorizados pela legislação aplicável, e serão eliminados posteriormente, a menos que (i) tenha levantado objecções à factura, ou (ii) exista uma suspeita razoável de fraude ou de outra actividade criminosa. Para fins de aplicação da lei, os Dados de tráfego são também armazenados em conformidade com a legislação aplicável para retenção de dados. Os Dados de tráfego armazenados ao abrigo desta segunda frase não podem ser utilizados por si para fins de reclamação de factura.

**Segurança e integridade de dados**

Dispomos de salvaguardas físicas, electrónicas e processuais para proteger as Informações do Cliente sob o nosso controlo contra a perda, má utilização e alteração. As Informações do Cliente que recolhemos são armazenadas de forma segura de modo a que sejam acedidas apenas pelo pessoal autorizado, contratantes e agentes da Pinger vinculados pelas obrigações de confidencialidade e são apenas publicadas ao abrigo das disposições desta Política de Protecção de Dados. O nosso processamento de Dados pessoais destina-se apenas aos fins para os quais foram recolhidos ou, na sua falta, de acordo com esta Política de Protecção de Dados e as leis de protecção de dados aplicáveis nacionais e na UE. Periodicamente, a Pinger efectua uma análise das suas práticas de privacidade para assegurar que as informações que recolhemos são necessárias para proporcionar ou melhorar os serviços que prestamos.

Informações pessoais de crianças  

Os sítios web da Pinger estão em conformidade com a Lei de Protecção da Privacidade Online das Crianças (“COPPA”, do inglês Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). A Pinger não recolhe conscientemente Dados pessoais de crianças com menos de 13 anos de idade através dos sítios web da Pinger. Adicionalmente, caso um utilizador se identifique como criança com menos de 13 anos nos sítios web da Pinger, a Pinger não irá recolher, armazenar ou utilizar quaisquer Dados pessoais desse utilizador. Além disso, caso a Pinger receba Dados pessoais que a Pinger descubra que foram fornecidos por uma criança com menos de 13 anos, a Pinger irá eliminar imediatamente esses Dados pessoais de forma segura.

**Ligações a sítios de terceiros**

Para sua conveniência, podemos fornecer hiperligações e/ou ligações a sítios de terceiros ou serviços a partir dos nossos sítios web ou dos nossos produtos ou serviços. A Pinger não é responsável por práticas de privacidade ou conteúdos desses sítios de terceiros.

**Acesso/eliminação das suas informações pessoais**

Se pretender que removamos os seus Dados pessoais da nossa base de dados, ou se pretender aceder aos Dados pessoais que foram recolhidos de si, pode contactar-nos utilizando os dados de contactos fornecidos abaixo. Após a conclusão dos serviços Pinger, os seus Dados pessoais serão eliminados. Determinados produtos e serviços nossos requerem a utilização dos Dados de aplicações e esses dados são armazenados pela Pinger e utilizados conforme descrito nesta Política de Protecção de Dados e em contratos do utilizador final para os produtos e serviços aplicáveis.

**Alterações da Política de Protecção de Dados**

A Pinger reserva-se o direito, de acordo com os nossos critérios, de alterar, actualizar ou modificar esta Política de Protecção de Dados em qualquer altura, ao publicar essa alteração, actualização ou modificação nos sítios web da Pinger, e a mesma entrará em vigor imediatamente após a publicação, e a Pinger pode fornecer através de quaisquer meios, incluindo, sem limitação, a publicação nos sítios web da Pinger, notificações dentro das aplicações da Pinger ou por correio electrónico. A continuação da sua utilização dos sítios web da Pinger e/ou produtos e serviços da Pinger posteriormente à publicação das alterações significará que aceita estas alterações. A utilização das informações que recolhemos está sujeita à Política de Protecção de Dados em vigor aquando da utilização.

Contacte-nos  

Se tiver quaisquer dúvidas ou preocupações relativamente a esta Política de Protecção de Dados, como quais os Dados pessoais que são guardados sobre si, envie-nos um e-mail para [info@pinger.com](mailto:info@pinger.com). Se recebermos reclamações formais relacionadas com a privacidade, faz parte da nossa política utilizar os recursos ao nosso dispor para comunicar com a parte reclamante acerca das suas dúvidas para resolver reclamações de privacidade. Para os fins desta Política de Protecção de Dados, a “Pinger” representará tanto a Pinger (UK) Ltd. como a Pinger International Ltd., dependendo do contrato de utilizador da entidade que tiver aceitado.

Última actualização a 1 de Março de 2012  

概要

本データ保護ポリシーでは、Pingerの製品、サービスおよびウェブサイトをご利用いただく際にPingerが収集・受信する個人データを含む、当社が保有するデータの取扱いについて説明します。

Pingerが収集および利用する情報

Pingerは、ユーザーがPingerの製品、サービスおよびウェブサイトを利用・アクセスする際にデータを収集します。収集されるデータには、個人データ、アプリ データ、トラフィック データ、共有データが含まれます（以下、総称して「顧客情報」といいます）。「個人データ」とは、ユーザー自身によって提供され、ユーザーの身元を直接的に特定するために使用される情報であり、例えば氏名、住所、電子メールアドレス、請求先情報、自宅の電話番号、自宅および勤務先の住所などが含まれます。当社ウェブサイトのパブリック エリアにアクセスするだけでは、個人データは収集されません。「アプリ データ」とは、Pingerのウェブサイト、製品、サービスの利用の性質についての情報であり、個人情報を含まない人口統計学的な情報です。アプリ データには、以下の情報が含まれます。IPアドレス、ドメイン サーバー、参照元／閲覧終了ページ、OS情報、ウェブ ブラウザの種類、タイム スタンプ（日付／時刻）、クリックストリーム（ページ遷移）データ。また、Pingerの製品およびサービスに関するアプリ データには、以下の情報が含まれます。デバイス識別名、Pingerサービスを利用して送受信されたメッセージ、それらのメッセージに関する情報、デバイスの種類、位置情報、ユーザーの年齢と性別の人口統計、ブラウザの種類、通信事業者の情報、Pinger製品の機能の利用に関する情報と統計。「共有データ」とは、ユーザー自身によって提供され、Pingerの製品またはサービスと一緒に利用されるデータであり、Pingerの製品またはサービスの利用の際にユーザーの行動によって第三者が利用可能な状態になる可能性のあるデータです。

**情報の利用と処理／共有と開示**

Pinger製品とサービスの提供、向上、および修正、ユーザーの認証、カスタマー サービスおよびサポートの提供、Pinger製品およびサービスを通じたユーザーとの通信、当社の製品およびサービスを通じた広告の配信および提供、Pinger製品の告知、不正行為の検出およびユーザー契約の遵守、Pinger製品およびサービスの利用を通じてユーザーが指示した内容に基づく共有データの送信、共有、保存などの目的のため、Pingerは顧客情報を利用および処理します。Pingerは、アメリカ合衆国に設置された当社のサーバー上、およびサーバーを増設する可能性のある他の国に設置される当社のサーバー上で、個人データを含む顧客情報を処理します。当社は、第三者の代理として、あるいは第三者を通じて、あるいは第三者の指示に従って、顧客情報を処理する場合があります。この第三者には、当社と提携する広告会社などが含まれます。ただし、このような処理は、ユーザーから当社に対して、明示的で、詳しく説明された、取り消し可能な同意が提供された場合にのみ行われます。

Pingerは、ユーザーから明示的で、詳しく説明された同意を取得せず、以下の状況に該当しない場合、いかなる顧客情報の貸与、売却、共有も行いません。

（i）Pingerは信頼できる第三者に対して、当社の代理として限定的な業務の遂行を依頼する場合があります。これには、ニュースレターの購読者への配信、要求された郵便物、電子メール、SMS、MMSの送受信、および音声通信、データの分析と処理（請求情報など）、広告配信、カスタマーサービスの提供などが含まれます。当社は、上記の情報を機密事項として取扱い、本データ保護ポリシーを遵守する方法で取扱うことをこれらの第三者に要求します。これらの第三者は、業務遂行に必要な個人データにアクセスする場合がありますが、当社は関連法によって要求される場合を除き、これらの第三者がユーザーの同意なしに、個人データを他の目的に利用することを許可しません。

（ii）Pingerは、アプリ データおよびユーザーの身元を特定できないような非個人情報を第三者と共有する場合があります。

（iii）Pingerは、法的に要求される場合、および行政当局から要請を受けた場合、法的要件に対応するために顧客情報を共有する場合があります。

（iv）Pingerは、ユーザー契約および関連法の検証または遵守の強制、不正行為の防止、セキュリティ上または技術的な問題の検知および予防、Pingerの製品、サービス、コンピュータ システム、またはウェブサイトの不正使用や権限のない使用の防止、または Pinger、その加入者や公共の権利、財産、または安全の侵害防止などの目的のため、顧客情報を共有する場合があります。

（v）Pingerは、顧客情報の利用が本データ保護ポリシーを遵守している場合に限り、事業継承者との間で顧客情報を共有したり、企業統合、合併、資産売却、またはその他の企業再編に関連して顧客情報を共有したりする場合があります。

（vi）ユーザーがPingerの製品あるいはサービスを通じて第三者から情報を受領すること、または第三者との間で情報を共有することに同意した場合、Pingerは第三者と顧客情報を共有する場合があります。このような第三者は、自らの定めるデータ保護ポリシーだけでなく、ユーザーとの間で契約を締結した場合は、その諸条件に従い、当該の顧客情報を処理、保存、保持し、これにアクセスします。ユーザーは、当該の契約および第三者のデータ保護ポリシーについて、その内容を注意深く検討する責任を負います。Pingerは、第三者との情報の共有について、ユーザーに対して一切の責任を負わず、またPingerは、これに関連するいかなる責任もすべて否認します。

（vii）ソフトウェアおよびサービスをユーザーに提供するため、Pingerは欧州連合（EU）域内および域外にある親会社および／または関連会社との間で顧客情報を共有する場合があります。これらの会社は、世界中のあらゆる国において、本データ保護ポリシーに従い、顧客情報の処理と保存を行う場合があります。

**クッキー（Cookie）**

ユーザーがPingerのサイトにアクセスする際、当社は、ユーザーのブラウザを特定するクッキーをユーザーのコンピュータに対して送信したり、アクセスしたページを記録するため、ピクセル タグ（ウェブ ビーコンとも呼ばれる）を使用する場合があります。当社は、クッキーやタグを利用してユーザーの好みを保存したり、利用に関する情報を追跡することによって、サービスの向上を図ります。大抵のブラウザでは、クッキーを無効にしたり、コンピュータにクッキーが送信される際に警告を発するよう設定できます。また、メッセージが開封されたかどうか、行動が取られたかどうかを確認するため、プロモーション用メッセージにもタグを挿入する場合があります。上記のサービスに対して、Pingerがユーザーのコンピュータや装置にクッキーやタグを導入する権利を有することについて、ユーザーはここに明示的に同意するものとします。クッキーを無効にすると、Pingerの製品やサービスの一部を利用できなくなる場合があります。

トラフィックデータ  

電子通信トラフィック データ（以下「トラフィック データ」）は、Pingerのサービス利用に関連して収集され、通信の終了時に請求上の目的で保存されますが、関連法で規定された最長保存期間を過ぎると消去されます。ただし、（i）ユーザーが請求内容に対して異議を申し立てた場合や、（ii）不正行為またはその他の犯罪行為が発生したと疑われる合理的な理由がある場合は、この限りではありません。法執行の目的上、トラフィック データは、データ保持の関連法に従って保存されます。なお、この2番目の条件に基づいて保存されたトラフィック データは、請求に関する紛争解決の目的にユーザーが使用することはできません。

**セキュリティとデータの保全**

当社は、管理下にある顧客情報の喪失、不正使用および改変を防止するため、物理的、電子的および手続き上のセーフガード機能を設けています。当社が収集する顧客情報は安全な方法で保存され、守秘義務を負い、アクセス権を有するPingerの社員、契約業者、代理業者のみがアクセスできます。また、本データ保護ポリシーの規定の下でのみ開示されます。当社による個人データの処理はデータを収集した目的の範囲内でのみ、あるいは本データ保護ポリシー、関連EU法、および各国のデータ保護法に従って処理されます。Pingerはプライバシー保護の慣行について定期的に検討を行い、当社が収集する情報が、当社によるサービスの提供や向上に必要であるかどうか確認します。

子供の個人情報  

Pingerのウェブサイトは、児童オンラインプライバシー保護法（Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act、「COPPA」）を遵守しています。Pingerは、13歳未満の子供からはPingerのウェブサイトを通じて故意に個人情報を収集しません。さらに、Pingerのウェブサイト上でユーザーによって自分の年齢が13歳未満であると表明された場合、Pingerはそのユーザーの個人データを収集、保存、利用することはありません。また、Pingerに対して送信された個人データが13歳未満の子供から提供されたと判明した場合、Pingerは即座にその個人データをセキュアな方法で削除します。

**第三者のサイトへのリンク**

ユーザーの便宜のため、当社のウェブサイト、製品、またはサービス上で、第三者のウェブサイトやサービスへのリンクおよび／または接続を提供する場合があります。Pingerは、これらの第三者のサイトのプライバシー保護の慣行やコンテンツについては責任を負いません。

**ユーザーの個人情報のアクセス／削除**

当社データベースから個人データを削除することを希望される場合、あるいは収集された個人データへのアクセスを希望される場合は、後述の問い合わせ先に記載された連絡先からPingerにご連絡ください。ユーザーの個人データは、Pingerのサービス終了時に削除されます。Pingerの製品およびサービスの中には、アプリ データの使用を必要とするものがあり、そのようなデータは当社が保持し、本データ保護ポリシーおよび当該製品・サービスに関連するエンドユーザー契約書に記載の方法で使用されます。

**データ保護ポリシーの修正**

Pingerは独自の裁量により、いつでも本データ保護ポリシーを変更、更新、修正する権利を有します。この変更、更新、修正は、Pingerのウェブサイト上に掲示されます。これらの変更、更新、修正は告知と同時に即時発効となります。この告知はPingerウェブサイト上の掲示、Pingerアプリケーション内での通知、電子メールやその他の方法でPingerにより行われる場合があります。変更の通知後、Pingerウェブサイトおよび／またはPingerの製品やサービスの利用を継続することによって、ユーザーはそれらの変更に同意したものと見なされます。当社が収集する情報の利用範囲は、それを利用する時点のデータ保護ポリシーの内容に従うものとします。

お問い合わせ先  

本データ保護ポリシーに関するご質問、ご不明点な点（例えば、どのような個人データが保存されるか）がございましたら、[info@pinger.com](mailto:info@pinger.com)まで電子メールにてお問い合わせください。当社では、プライバシーに関して正式な苦情申立てを受けた場合、苦情を行った当事者との間で申立て内容についてのコミュニケーションを図り、プライバシーに関する苦情を解決するための合理的な努力を払います。本データ保護ポリシーにおいて、「Pinger」とはPinger (UK) Ltd.またはPinger International Ltd.のいずれかを指します。これは、ユーザーが同意したユーザー契約がどちらの会社から発行されたものかに依存します。

最終更新日：2012年3月1日

**Privacy**

#### Homepage

#### Products

#### Download apps

#### CONTACT

* 97 S. 2nd St. Suite 210  
    San Jose, CA 95113

#### Homepage

#### Products

#### Download APps

#### CONTACT

* 97 S. 2nd St. Suite 210  
    San Jose, CA 95113

© 2024 Pinger, Inc.    [Privacy](https://www.pinger.com/privacy)    [Terms](https://www.pinger.com/terms)    [Beta Agreement](https://www.pinger.com/beta-agreement)  

© 2024 Pinger, Inc.  

© 2023 Fortune Media IP Limited. All rights reserved. Used under license.
